JOI YAN RONG HUANG

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

San José Costa Rica

PHONE

(506) 7277-3018

EMAIL

rhhaiyin@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

05/26/1989 Costa Rica

SKILLS

Fast Learner

Analytical and Problem-Solving skills

Javascript

HTML & CSS

Git & GitHub

WordPress development

Responsive Web Design

Programming paradigms & principles

Online marketing optimization

CSS frameworks

LANGUAGES

Spanish

.

English

• • • •

French

• • • 0 0

LINKS

<u>Website</u>

PROFILE

I'm a front-end web developer with over 3 years of experience. I get a kick out of problem solving and learning about new technologies. I can create beautiful websites with clean and responsive code and web applications that are fully interactive in Javascript. I'd love to work with a team of passionate people, driven about their work, collaborative and have a positive attitude.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

E-mail Deployment Specialist, Cheetah Digital

Mar 2017 — Aug 2021

- Set up of e-mail campaigns using HTML and CSS.
- Quality assurance throughout all stages of deployment.
- E-mail design & coding best practices.
- Working with database segmentation.
- Creating Account documentation and guidelines.
- Training new team members.
- Client facing communication.

Technical Support Specialist, Concentrix

Dec 2013 — Oct 2016

- Providing support in English and French speaking customers to resolve device issues. Troubleshooting connectivity issues with devices and assessment of best solution for the customer. Interacting with different cultural backgrounds.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, Universidad Estatal a Distancia de Costa Rica

Jan 2019 — Present

Business Administration Diploma, Universidad Estatal a Distancia de Costa Rica

May 2018 — Present

Responsive Web Design, freecodecamp.org

Certificate Credential

Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures, freecodecamp.org

Certificate Credential

Edline Monge from Cheetah Digital - Campaign Manager

https://tinyurl.com/52yb5s3e | edline.monge@cheetahdigital.com